Hey. You ready?
All right. Secret sign.
Hey, Ryan.
Very good. Excellent. Excellent.
Michael.
Today at lunchtime we're
going to be playing the warehouse staff
at a friendly little game
of basketball. My idea.
I noticed they'd put up a couple of hoops
and I play basketball every weekend
so I thought, "This might be kinda fun."
And I started messing around and...I'm sinking
a few, you know. Swish, swish.
Nothing but net.
And their jaws just dropped to the floor.
African-Americans, so...
You know, it's really just a good
friendly game, a reason to get together.
Pam, Pam, thank you, ma'am.
Messages, please.
Michael, can I talk to you, please?
Privately? In your office?
- I think I should be on the team.
- No.
That's not me being mean.
- That is based on your past behavior.
- Please.
When I let him come to
my pick-up game...
- I apologized for that.
- I vouched for you.
I vouched for you in front
of Todd Packer, Dwight.
All right, here's what I'm gonna do.
The hand strikes and gives a flower.
You are not going to play basketball.
But I need somebody to come in
and take over the holiday
and weekend work calendar.
- I can handle that.
- Good.
Excellent. It'll be fun.
Because Corporate wants somebody
to be here on Saturday
and so we have to have some people
come in on the weekend,
and I know everybody's
gonna complain and bitch
and I don't wanna deal with that.
It's why you have an assistant manager.
Yes, it is.
Assistant to the regional manager.
- Same thing.
- No, it's not. It's lower, so...
It's close.
So we need someone to work this Saturday
and I think that should be...
- Jim.
- God, this is so sad.
This is the smallest amount of power
I've ever seen go to someone's head.
- Phyllis, can you believe this?
- Keep me out of it.
My fiancé has plans for us this Saturday
so I really hope
Dwight doesn't make me work.
Maybe I should sleep with him?
I'm kidding. Kidding.
Totally kidding.
All right! Managing by walking around!
This is our warehouse.
Or, as I like to call it, the whorehouse.
- Don't you do that. I've earned the right.
- Fine, don't worry about that.
And here we have
"Mister Roger's Neighborhood".
Come on over here. Hey, this is Ryan.
- He's temping upstairs.
- What's up?
- This is the foreman, Mister Rogers.
- Not my real name.
No, Darryl is Mister Rogers.
- Darryl Rogers?
- Darryl Philbin.
Then Regis, then Rege, then Roger,
then Mister Rogers.
And that is Lonny. And this is Roy.
Roy dates Pam.
The best-looking one upstairs.
- Yeah.
- You still getting it regular, man, huh?
I mean, I can tell her it's part of the job.
Rapport.
No, I know that the warranty's expired
but isn't it supposed to last longer
than two years if it isn't defective?
OK, fine, three years.
Pam gets a little down.
Her toaster oven broke.
Which she got at her engagement shower.
For a wedding that still has yet to be set.
And that was three years ago.
So, one o'clock sharp
and we've got a game on.
- We're loading at one.
- I see, you're chickening out on me.
No, we got a truck going out at 1:15.
That's the busy time.
Well, I'm glad that some time is a busy time
because whenever I'm down here
it doesn't seem too busy to me.
Oh. Oh. You can dish it out but you
can't take it. OK, fine, have it your way.
All right, fine, you know what?
One o'clock.
All right, see you at one.
Are we ready for the game?
Yeah.
I know. Grumble, grumble,
but you would follow me to the
ends of the earth, grumbling all the way.
Like that dwarf from Lord Of The Rings.
- Gimli.
- Nerd. That is why you're not on the team.
- Just trying to be helpful.
- "I'll help. Elwyn Dragonslayer...
"Ten points, power sword."
That's him.
So let's put together a starting line-up,
shall we?
- Stanley, of course.
- I'm sorry?
- What do you play, center?
- Why "of course"?
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know. I don't remember saying that.
- I heard it.
- Well, people hear a lot of things, man.
Um...other starters... Me, of course.
I heard it that time.
I'd like to play if it's just for fun.
I played basketball in school.
Um... Yeah. Who else? We have Jim.
We have Ryan, the new guy, right?
Untested. Willing to prove himself now.
A lot of passion, a lot of heart.
- I'm getting paid to skip lunch?
- Yes.
- OK.
- Yes. This is business.
The business of team building
and morale boosting.
- Uh...who else?
- I can help out if you need me.
I will use your talents
come baseball season. Or if we box.
- I have a hoop in my driveway.
- No.
- I have a sports bra.
- No, ridiculous.
Michael, look.
Close. All right. Uh...
Me, Stan the man,
Jim, Ryan and Dwight.
- Yes!
- Sorry, Phyllis.
- Can I be captain?
- No, I am.
- Can I be team manager?
- You're assistant to the manager.
- Assistant team manager?
- No.
OK, we'll see who's working
this weekend then.
- Jim, take over the vacation schedule.
- Oh, my God.
Threat neutralized.
Off the backboard!
- Please don't throw garbage at me.
- Oh, Pam, with a zinger.
Hey, Pam, how would you
like to be our cheerleader today?
You know, some pigtails,
a little halter top, tie that up.
And something a little,
just, youthful, for a change.
- Just this once.
- I don't think so, Michael.
Besides, I can't cheer
against my fiancé.
I'll do it. Wear a little flouncey skirt
if you want, and...
I bet you would. Just try not to be
too gay on the court.
And by gay I mean...you know,
not in a homosexual way at all.
I mean the uh, you know,
like the bad-at-sports way.
- I think that goes without saying.
- Maybe Angela would cheerlead.
- Yeah, right.
- I'll do it.
Yuk. That's worse than you playing.
Cos we need you as an alternate
in case somebody gets hurt.
That's where we need you.
Blessed be those who sit and wait.
You made it.
Suit up, you're on the team!
All right, cool!
Very good.
Oh-oh. Oh-oh. A spy from the warehouse.
Trying to figure out our plays?
- Just getting a tea bag.
- He's running.
He's running but he can't hide
because one o'clock,
you better bring your A game.
Because me and my posse guys
are gonna be in your face.
- Right in your face!
- Why don't we make it more interesting?
Loser buys dinner at Farley's.
Wo-ho. I like the way you think.
I'm gonna take that one step further.
Loser works on Saturday.
No, that's not as much fun.
- You know what?
- What?
- You're on.
- OK.
Cool. You're on.
Don't screw this up.
Classic beginner's mistake -
eating before a game.
Has anyone seen the first-aid kit?
How many times have I told you?
I'm the safety officer, not you.
Basketball? It was my thing in high school.
And, yeah, I'm looking forward to playing.
I think I'm gonna impress
a few people in here.
- You coming down?
- Yeah, I'm just forwarding the phones.
- Gonna wish me luck?
- Yeah, you're gonna need it.
Is that trash talk from Pam?
I'm just saying, Roy is very competitive
and he wants to take the WaveRunner
to the lake this Saturday so...
Well, I'm going to the outlet mall
on Saturday,
so if you wanna save big on brand names,
and Roy has to work, which he will,
because I'm also competitive,
you should feel free to come along.
Um...I think I'm gonna be up at the lake.
I think I'll see you at the mall. Yeah.
Hey. There he is. Secret weapon!
All right, guys, come on,
let's bring it in! Here we go!
OK, listen, this is just going to be
a friendly game, right?
We are all on the same team here.
The Dunder Mifflin team.
Of course, if you beat us you're fired.
That's a joke.
OK, let's do it!
- Have a good game.
- Yeah, you too. Should be fun.
All right, everybody stretch out a little bit.
Stretch it.
- Ryan, you wanna stretch?
- I stretched before I came.
OK, Ryan, you have Darryl. I have Roy.
- Really? I thought I'd take Roy.
- Roy is their best player, not Lonny.
So, Dwight, you have the East German gal.
Um... OK. All right, you guys!
- OK, we'll be skins...
Come on, Dwight.
- What? Shirts on or off?
- On. Just put it on.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Pam? You have your foot in both camps,
why don't you do the jump ball, OK?
Don't listen to him. Tip it my way
or you're sleeping in the car.
Stanley!
What? You gotta be kidding me?
Oh...
Here we go!
Who's on him? Somebody get him!
- Yeah!
- That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Over here!
Three! Go to zone! We're going to zone!
Defense! Defense!
- Well done, team!
- Who's got Roy?
Woo!
Come on, what is wrong with me today?
Usually hit those.
Dwight, I was open.
All right, let's go.
Yo, Jerry!
OK, foul. Charging. Charging.
That's a foul. OK, I'll take it.
When I am playing hoops,
all of the stress and responsibility
of my job here just melts away.
It's gone. I'm in the zone.
Who am I? Am I Michael Scott?
I don't know.
I might just be a basketball machine.
What's Dunder Mifflin?
I've never heard of it.
Filing? Paperwork? Who cares?
Possible downsizing?
Um.... Well, that's probably
gonna happen, actually.
Jim! Jim! Jim, right here! Jim!
Give me the ball! Ryan, cut!
My bad.
- Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
- Uh, uh, uh.
Where you at? Where you at?
You over there? I'm over here. Oh! Uh!
That is cool. Is that like The Robot?
- Nice!
- Come here!
Can we just do one?
That's cool. That's fine.
- Come on.
- All right, let's go.
- Watch your back, Madge!
- Back off, man!
Come on! Hey, Dwight! Dwight!
Yeah! In your face!
- Like that counts.
- You know what? Dwight...
Football is like rock and roll,
it's just bam-bam-boo...
And basketball is like jazz, you know?
You're kind of...
♪ Dupee-doo, dupee-do ♪
It's all downbeat, it's in the pocket, it's like...
♪ Dupee-do, dupee-do, dapee-dah ♪
♪ Du-du-du-du-dupee-do,
de-do-do-do
de-do-do-do... ♪
♪ Du-du-du-du-dupee-do ♪
- Your ball.
- All right, time, time out.
Come on, Sales, over here.
Bring it in! Come on!
What's going on?
You're playing like a bunch of girls.
- Let me take Roy.
- All right, switch.
Take it up a notch, come on.
Shoot it, shoot it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Foul! Naked aggression!
Oh, that is... You all right, Jim? Suck it up.
He's afraid of you now.
Ouch! Oh, how much does it hurt?
How much does it hurt?
Yes!
- What the hell, man?
- Take it easy.
No, you take it easy.
Give me the ball. Come on.
Watch the long passes, you guys!
Same team, Dwight.
Yes!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! In your face!
- Angela, what's the score?
- You're ahead.
Yeah, baby, here we go!
Jim! Jim!
Right here! Ow, God! Hold it!
- I'm sorry.
- Foul! Foul!
- I'm sorry. You all right?
- Oh, that hurts.
- Sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
- What's your problem, man?
Just clocking me for no reason.
- Take your shot, man!
- No, no, no, no.
- That was a flagrant, intentional foul.
- No, it wasn't!
Yes, it was! I'm just being fair.
- No, I just put my arm up...
- Game over. That is it!
I'm sorry, you know?
I hate to do it this way
but, you know, that's just...
We're having a friendly game.
It's a shame!
This is a damn shame
but we're like
a family here and that won't fly.
- This is a cold pack.
- You have to break the bag.
- Thanks, Dwight.
- Wait, what does that mean?
What, is it a tie? What's going on?
Let's say whoever was ahead won.
- That was you.
- It was us? Really?
I didn't know.
Great, I mean, I guess you guys
are working Saturday.
- Your face.
- No, I'm not coming in on Saturday.
Yeah, this isn't happening.
Um...
Well, guys, you know, I'm the boss so...
So what's that?
We're coming in on Monday, right?
Hey. Hey.
Monday?
You guys believed me? Come on.
Dogs, you know,
you should know me better than that.
Do you think that would've been
good for morale? No. No. No.
Exactly. No. I'm embarrassed
it was even that close though.
No, of course, we're coming in Saturday.
Good game. Word.
So I talked to this scout. It looks good.
I didn't sign anything.
Hey, baby.
Look at Larry Bird. Larry Legend.
Yeah, he's pretty good, huh?
Let's get you into a tub.
Yeah, let's get you in a tub.
Hey. What a game, huh?
What a game.
- What time do we have to come in?
- Come on. Let's not be gloomy.
We're all in this together. We're a team.
You know what? Screw Corporate,
nobody's coming in tomorrow.
You have the day off.
Like coming in an extra day is gonna
prevent us from being downsized.
Have a good weekend.
The great thing about sports
is that it is all about character.
And you can learn lessons about life
even if you don't win.
But we did because we were ahead.